Guide to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture records, 1954-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture records 1954-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture
26.9 linear feet Extent: 15,500 Items
On a 1957 trip to India and China, Doris Duke stopped in Thailand, and it is likely that the exploration of Bangkok and its art and architecture she saw on that visit inspired her to dream of creating a Thai village in Hawaii with houses similar to those she had seen. In December of 1960, she formally hired François Duhau de Berenx to help bring it to pass. The Thai House Foundation was established on January 30, 1961; the name was changed to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC) in June of that same year. The establishment of the Foundation resulted in a project that Doris Duke saw as a gift to Hawaii, and one that occupied her for many years. At least five sites in Hawaii were considered for the Thai Village and it was the choice of an appropriate location that ultimately proved the stumbling block to completion of the project. Although her dream of a Thai Village was never fulfilled, Doris Duke's interest in Asia continued, as she continued purchasing objects right up until her death in 1993. In 2002, a significant portion of the collection was donated to two museums distinguished for their collections of Southeast Asian art; the Asian Art Museum of San Francisco and the Walters Art Museum in Baltimore. The collection documents the establishment and management of Doris Duke's Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC). Records in the Administrative series document the purchase and transport of art objects and building parts, Doris Duke's attempts to locate a site for the Thai Village, and the financial records associated with the daily operations and management of the foundation and its assets. The Photograph series consists primarily of black and white images of the art objects and building parts purchased for SEAAC, with some images of houses in Bangkok and other Thai buildings, which served as the inspiration for the Thai Village. The architectural records in this collection include various drawings of the proposed village site and plans for the various buildings that were to be constructed.
RL.01441
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use. Due to the fragility of the architectural records, The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Digital use copies in this collection have been migrated to a library server and can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access please contact a reference archivist prior to visiting the library.
Provenance
The Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a donation from the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation in June 2009.
Historical Note
Doris Duke was an avid world traveler and it was in Asia that she found inspiration for many of the projects she subsequently undertook, including her collection of Asian art. On a 1957 trip to India and China, Doris Duke stopped in Thailand. It is likely that the exploration of Bangkok and its art and architecture she saw on that visit inspired her to dream of creating a Thai village in Hawaii with houses similar to those she had seen. More than a year passed before Doris Duke's idea of constructing the village was formalized, and in December of 1960, she formally hired François Duhau de Berenx, a decorator and art dealer, to help bring it to pass (Berenx was the first Curator of SEAAC). The Thai House Foundation was established on January 30, 1961; the name was changed to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC) in June of that same year. The establishment of the Foundation resulted in a project that Doris Duke saw as a gift to Hawaii, and one that occupied her for many years.
At least five sites in Hawaii were considered for the Thai Village and it was the choice of an appropriate location that ultimately proved the stumbling block to completion of the project. While Doris Duke continued to purchase art objects and made plans for additional buildings, between 1966 and 1972, she continued to try to find a site for the village. At the end of 1972, she and Leon Amar began installing SEAAC in the Coach Barn at Duke Farms, and during 1973 and 1974 made several trips to Southeast Asia to purchase objects. Although her dream of a Thai Village was never fulfilled, Doris Duke's interest in Asia continued, as she continued purchasing objects right up until her death in 1993.
In 2002, a significant portion of the collection was donated to two museums distinguished for their collections of Southeast Asian art; the Asian Art Museum of San Francisco and the Walters Art Museum in Baltimore.
Collection Overview
The Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture Records (formerly SEAAC.8) are part of the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation Historical Archives which were donated to the Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation. The collection spans the years 1954 to 2002, and is arranged in three series: Administrative Records, Photographs, and Architectural Records. The collection documents the establishment and management of Doris Duke's Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture. Records in the Administrative series reveal a frenzied few years of acquisition, where the curator of SEAAC sought works of art of all types - manuscript cabinets and manuscripts, Thai ceramics, Chinese porcelains, wood, stone, bronze and ivory sculptures, and complete Thai houses. It also documents Doris Duke's attempts to locate a site for the Thai Village, the transport and exhibition of the objects at the Coach Barn at Duke Farms, and the financial records associated with the daily operations and management of the foundation and its assets. The Photograph series consists primarily of black and white images of the art objects and building parts purchased for SEAAC, with some images of houses in Bangkok and other Thai buildings, which served as the inspiration for the Thai Village. The architectural records in this collection include various drawings of the proposed village site and plans for the various buildings that were to be constructed. The materials in this collection are arranged loosely in chronological order.
Subject Headings
Architecture -- Designs and plans; Architectural drawing -- United States -- 20th Century; Art, Southeast Asian; Duke, Doris, 1912-1993; Hawaii; Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture
Related Material
Doris Duke Papers on the Shangri La Residence, 1932-2003
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke Family Papers on the Duke Farms Residence, 1859-2004 and undated
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Contents of Collection
- Administrative Records, 1960-2002 and undated
  Materials include correspondence and memoranda related to the creation and general administrative matters of the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC), inventories, packing lists, customs entries and exhibition bonds of purchased art objects from Southeast Asia, estimates and bills related to construction of various buildings, and the Certificate of Incorporation, Amendments, and By-Laws of the Thai House Foundation (renamed SEAAC). Also included are tax returns, financial summaries, ledgers, and other financial records. Topics include land discussions and possible sites in Hawaii for the Thai Village, admission procedures and ticket sales, administrative expenses, the purchase and shipment of art objects, the construction of several buildings, and the daily operations of the Foundation.
  - Correspondence written to Francois Duhau de Berenx in his capacity as curator for SEAAC. Includes letter from Doris Duke to de Berenx and other materials (letters are photocopies of originals still with de Berenx). 1960–1963, 1986, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1961–1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence relating to land discussions for Thai Village. 1961–1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, to/from Louis Pursel, A.I.A. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence relating to SEAAC’s membership with the American Association of Museums. 1962–1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, to/from Francois Duhau de Berenx. 1962–1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1963 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1963 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to Board of Directors information. 1963–1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1963–1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to land discussions around the Kahana properties. 1963–1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to land discussions in Haiku Valley (Bishop Estate). 1963–1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and memoranda to/from Dr. Mung Yee, Director of SEAAC. Includes transcripts of phone conferences. 1963–1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence relating to land discussions. 1963–1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to the construction of the Thai Pavilion. 1963–1967 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to the construction of the Thai Pavilion. 1963–1967 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, application, and related materials concerning SEAAC’s enrollment with the Hawaii Foreign Annual Eleemosynary Corporation Exhibits. 1963, 1968–1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and related materials concerning the transport of two Thai miniatures. 1964–1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to land discussions of the Kahana property. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1965–1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to general administrative matters. 1966–1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Letter discussing a possible site in Hawaii for Thai Village. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and related materials concerning Disability Insurance, Hawaii. 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence relating to SEAAC’s achievement of tax exemption status. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence relating to Doris Duke’s dealings with Park Travel Agency and the shipment of objects to N.J. 1972–1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda relating to security matters with The Animal Medical Center. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and related materials concerning admission procedures and ticket sales. 1973–1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to Leon Amar. Includes some financial data. 1973–1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Administrative materials, variety of topics. 1973–1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence relating to the transport of objects to N.J. 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and related diagrams pertaining to the possibility of painting the SEAAC Thai Pagoda with a coating to protect its carvings and glass mosaics from the outside elements. Letter is to Robert Weniger from Hiram Sadd, Benjamin Moore & Co. January 14, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda relating to possible purchases made for the SEAAC collection. 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Invoices and receipts relating to travel to Thailand, Burma, and India. March 1961–April 1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Receipts of brokerage transactions with the Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1961–1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Financial materials and related correspondence (copies). Ledger notes most likely belong to George Reed. 1961–1974, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Trial balance, assets, liabilities, and capital, income and expenses. 1961–1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Invoices, SEAAC purchases. 1962–1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Administrative expenses, trial balances. 1962–1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tax forms relating to federal taxes and FICA taxes. 1963–1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Financial documents relating to Hawaii income tax. 1963–1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Financial documents relating to Hawaii unemployment taxes. 1963–1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Estimate, construction of Thai temple, Thai Koon Seng Ltd. Partnership. c. 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Invoices and receipts relating to travel to Tokyo, Bangkok, and Hong Kong. 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Estimates and bills relating to the construction of the Thai temple. 1964–1965 (copies made from originals housed at Shangri La) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Tax returns, Form 990. 1964–1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Invoices and vouchers relating to objects purchased by SEAAC. 1968–1974 (copies) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Summary statements. 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Financial materials and related correspondence concerning general tax matters. 1969–1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bank Statements with First Hawaiian Bank. 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Financial materials relating to general administrative matters. 1970–1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Financial materials organized for Wesley N. Fach. 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Audit of 1969 federal tax return. 1971–1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Invoice for moving and shipping one standing Buddha and base to N.J. 1971–1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Payroll summaries, Hawaii. 1971–1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Air waybills for the transport of paintings and tapestries. 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bills of lading, Seatrain lines, and Central Railroad of N.J. 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Invoices and related materials concerning the transport of objects by Sofield Transfer Co., Inc. and Seatrain Lines. 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Payroll summaries, M.G.T. Account, No. 165-11-499. 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Trial Balance, N.Y. Office. 1972–1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1972–1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Payroll summaries, Management Account, No. 165-11-499. 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Financial materials relating to Federal Payroll taxes. 1973–1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, receipts, and related materials concerning the shipment of purchases made in Thailand. 1973–1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Contributions to N.J. Division of Unemployment and Disability Insurance. 1973–1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Payroll summaries, Management Account, No. 165-11-499. 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Financial materials relating to general administrative matters. 1974–1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Payroll summaries, Management Account, No. 165-11-499. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1975–1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Payroll summaries, Management Account, No. 165-11-499. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Payroll summaries, Management Account, No. 165-11-499. 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1979–1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1980–1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1986–1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Invoice and related materials concerning silk fabrics purchased for SEAAC collection. Includes copy of exhibit script (November 1986). 1986, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tax returns, Form 990 – pF. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Policy of Title Insurance, Washington Title Insurance. 1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, Amendments, and By-laws of the Thai House Foundation. 1961, 1964, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Corporation Power of Attorney. 1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Agreement, F. Duhau and SEAAC/Doris Duke pertaining to final services provided by employee after termination with SEAAC. June 30, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Contract for the construction of the Thai Pavilion. 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Consent of Action in Lieu of Meeting of Members of SEAAC. 1978, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Catalog and copies of catalogs relating to the SEAAC collection. Some copies indicate location of pieces with handwritten notes in red pen. c. 1960s (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Catalog and copies of catalogs relating to the SEAAC collection. Some copies indicate location of pieces with handwritten notes in red pen. c. 1960s (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Summary, partial, describing SEAAC Village and Foundation. c. 1960s. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Inventories of art objects. 1960–1970 (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Inventories of art objects. 1960–1970 (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Inventories, packing lists, and related materials concerning the shipment of art objects. 1961–1966 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Inventory, “Francois Collection.” c. 1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Report, “The Ahupuaa of Kahana: Information concerning its topography, ownership and development potential.” c. 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Report, Thai Village Sites, Punaluu, Oahu (Bishop Estate). August 27, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Franchise Tax Reports, State of Delaware. 1969–1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Inventory of Art Objects for SEAAC. Includes date of purchase, invoice No., entry No., dealer, object description, and cost. 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - List of articles crated for transport. c. 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Inventory (partial) of art objects. 1972–1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Inventory of art objects. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Summary of SEAAC exhibit in the Coach Barn and background on Thailand. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Declarations, Bureau of Customs. 1960–1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Note, re: photos of Thai house submitted by Pursel and Associates. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Specifications, Thai-Style Water Pavilion to be erected in Hawaii. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Fact Sheet and background information about SEAAC collection to answer questions of guests visiting display. 1972, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tour script of SEAAC exhibit in Coach Barn. 1986 (rev. 1997) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 2748. October 20, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0320. November 16, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0321. November 16, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0322. November 16, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0323. November 16, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0324. November 16, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - SEAAC: Customs Entry 0326. November 17, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0327. November 17, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0328. November 17, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 3590. November 17, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0336. November 20, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0337. November 20, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0338. November 20, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0347. November 27, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0391. December 26, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - SEAAC: Consumption Entries. 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0440. February 2, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0485. February 19, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 12, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0533. March 14, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0534. March 14, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. April 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. April 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. May 24, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 12, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 12, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 27, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 23, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 23, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. August 17, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - SEAAC: Customs entry 0278. October 24, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - SEAAC: Consumption Entries. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. January 9, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. February 20, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 4, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 4, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 11, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 11, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 11, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 21, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. March 21, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. May 9, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. May 9, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. June 26, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 25, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 26. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 26, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. July 31, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. August 27, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. August 30, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. August 30, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. August 30, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. October 11, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. October 15, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - SEAAC: Permanent Exhibition Bond. October 15, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General Ledger, 1978-1998 (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 24)